<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Ywamuyu || My Calming Chaos</title>
        <link>https://ywamuyu.com</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:52:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2022 Y Wamuyu</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dear Little Girl]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/Dear-Little-Girl</link>
            <guid>Dear-Little-Girl</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[You are not too much.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[### Dear Little girl 
You are not a second choice 


They didnt choose you because you are not worthy 


But because they weren't built to love you 


I know their arms feel like they were supposed to carry you


But the lack of their strength is not a testimony of the weight of your soul


But rather the weakness of theirs.


You are not too much.




### Sincerely, Your big sister.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Like mother, like daughter]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/Heeey-Wammzz</link>
            <guid>Heeey-Wammzz</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Some days I open my mouth and my mother comes out. Each word is 
a riot. I find myself slipping into her anger with so much ease it shocks me
sometimes. The world is burning and everyone is waiting foe her to put out her flames with her tears because her pain is used to heal everyone else. 


I have inherited the rage that comes with being a safe haven for visitors 
who leave without cleaning up their mess. My mother didn't invent pain but 
my God, does she wear it well. My mother doesnt flinch as she pulls out the knives in her back and rinses off the blood to forget there was ever a time she was vulnerable to the wrong people. 


My other gives me heirlooms like backbone and strength, and hand-me-down trauma, because I come from a long line of women who bleed on command, and 
cry only when everyone else is asleep. 


An eon ago; I broke this rule when I rushed back home and bawled in my mother's lap because I gave my name to a boy and he returned it broken and damaged and bruised. My mother stroked my hair and laughed softly when I told her that the pain was overwhelming. 
"My child," she said "sadly this won't be the last time you cry in my arms."

****

]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Something smart]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/Intro</link>
            <guid>Intro</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Talking about something really smart.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
### Happy 22 btw!!]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>