<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Ywamuyu || My Calming Chaos</title>
        <link>https://ywamuyu.com</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 09:19:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2022 Y Wamuyu</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I cried on my drive home yesterday]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/apathetic-mood</link>
            <guid>apathetic-mood</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[I cried on my drive home yesterday. Now normally I would 
not talk about something like this but lately Ive been trying 
to acknowledge my emotions instead of crumpling them up or 
lighting them on fire or swallowing them whole. so i'll tell you. 


I cried on my drive home yesterday because the thought of getting there and parking my car and putting my key in the lock and transferring all the heat 
from my hand to the surface of the handle just to step inside and transfer all of the heat from my body to the surface of the air made me put my foot on the gas and never stop accelerating. Newton told us that a body in motion 
stays in motion and the thought of arriving and feeling all of my warmth drain my blood into the mouth of a leech made me want to prove him right. 


But im so tired of it really. Im tired of running and im tired of writing 
about what home really means and im tired of trying to find the right answers to questions I don't even know how to ask. 


How do you go back to a bedroom that feels like a graveyard, where the only things that disturb the dust are the ghosts passing through?
How do you heal in a house that only reminds you of your own hurt? 
How are you supposed to give all you have and survive at the same time? Is it a victory to conquer race living in today?


Tomorrow, I will live more simply. I will wash my face as the  coffee brews. 
I will hang my clean clothes in the closet. I will sit in the sun for a while. When my sister calls to tell me about her exams at school, I will answer. When the afternoon melts into evening, i'll pull the weeds from the flowerbeds. The ground will not give beneath me, the rhythm in my chest will not falter. 


I become so confused by the drastic that sometimes I forget mondanities exist. That there are rests between the notes and there are other things other than noise. I am trying to entangle myself from the adult desire to proceed without pausing. I'm trying to refrain from turning everything into some inevitable countdown to some inevitable end. 

]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Like mother, like daughter]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/Heeey-Wammzz</link>
            <guid>Heeey-Wammzz</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Some days I open my mouth and my mother comes out. Each word is 
a riot. I find myself slipping into her anger with so much ease it shocks me
sometimes. The world is burning and everyone is waiting for her to put out her flames with her tears because her pain is used to heal everyone else. 


I have inherited the rage that comes with being a safe haven for visitors 
who leave without cleaning up their mess. My mother didn't invent pain but 
my God, does she wear it well. My mother doesnt flinch as she pulls out the knives in her back and rinses off the blood to forget there was ever a time she was vulnerable to the wrong people. 


My mother gives me heirlooms like backbone and strength, and hand-me-down trauma, because I come from a long line of women who bleed on command, and 
cry only when everyone else is asleep. 


An eon ago; I broke this rule when I rushed back home and bawled in my mother's lap because I gave my name to a boy and he returned it broken and damaged and bruised. My mother stroked my hair and laughed softly when I told her that the pain was overwhelming. 
"My child," she said "sadly this won't be the last time you cry in my arms."

****

]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dear Little Girl]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/Dear-Little-Girl</link>
            <guid>Dear-Little-Girl</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[You are not too much.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[### Dear Little girl 
You are not a second choice 


They didnt choose you because you are not worthy 


But because they weren't built to love you 


I know their arms feel like they were supposed to carry you


But the lack of their strength is not a testimony of the weight of your soul


But rather the weakness of theirs.


You are not too much.




### Sincerely, Your big sister.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Something smart]]></title>
            <link>https://ywamuyu.composts/Intro</link>
            <guid>Intro</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Talking about something really smart.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
### Happy 22 btw!!]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>